{
    "subject": "Nicky_Henson",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Una_Stubbs",
    "human_readable": "Nicky Henson is married to Una Stubbs.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9885407090187073,
            "question": "Is Una Stubbs married to Nicky Henson?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9870795607566833,
            "question": "Is there a known marriage between Nicky Henson and Una Stubbs?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9836000204086304,
            "question": "Who are the spouses of Nicky Henson and Una Stubbs?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9455640912055969,
            "question": "Are Nicky Henson and Una Stubbs in a marital relationship?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9282350540161133,
            "question": "Who is Nicky Henson married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8819838166236877,
            "question": "To whom is Una Stubbs married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8706888556480408,
            "question": "Who is the wife of Nicky Henson?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8002759218215942,
            "question": "Are Nicky Henson and Una Stubbs related?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7534810304641724,
            "question": "What is the name of Nicky Henson's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7533247470855713,
            "question": "Can you name the husband of Una Stubbs?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Nicky Henson is married to Una Stubbs.",
            "html": "yago_9865_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Nicky Henson's spouse?",
            "html": "yago_9865_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are Nicky Henson and Una Stubbs related?",
            "html": "yago_9865_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is the wife of Nicky Henson?",
            "html": "yago_9865_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9865_109.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9865_115.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9865_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9865_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9865_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9865_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9865_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9865_95.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9865_96.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9865_98.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple \"Nicky Henson is married to Una Stubbs\" based on the provided context information:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide evidence that Nicky Henson was indeed married to Una Stubbs, as mentioned in multiple files (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_9865/re-ranker-msmarco/72.txt, file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_9865/re-ranker-msmarco/95.txt, and file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_9865/re-ranker-msmarco/118.txt)."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that confirms Nicky Henson and Una Stubbs were married. Specifically, the document at file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_9865/re-ranker-msmarco/43.txt states, \"Nicky Henson and Una Stubbs are divorced after a marriage of 6 years.\" This indicates they were indeed married at some point."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "There are multiple statements indicating Nicky Henson and Una Stubbs were divorced after a marriage of six years.",
            "category": 0
        }
    }
}